

Computer Science | University of Waterloo

≥ t225yang@uwaterloo.ca 647-528-6998 to www.linkedin.com/in/TianhuiYang www.github.com/TianhuiYang thttps://TianhuiYang.me

I am a **confident communicator** and **reliable team player**, developed through my **4-year** involvement in debate and DECA. In addition to my **interpersonal skills**, I have experience in **back-end** and **web development** and desire to continue growing.

PROJECTS

- WINNER in 3 categories (view awards section)
- A fully functioning map-services web app that displays top
 Instagram photography locations using Google Maps API, Node.js
- Used Python to scrape IG data, deployed using heroku and AWS

HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery | Dec. 2019 - Present

- Used HTML/CSS to design a functioning website
- Implemented animations using JavaScript and jQuery

Rhetorical Devices Tutorial

Java, Java Swing | June 2019

- Coded a GUI using Java to help students learn rhetorical devices
- Used Swing for the front-end to incorporate responsive buttons

EXPERIENCE

National Lead — Illuminate Universe

Toronto, ON | Aug. 2019 - Present

- Planned and executed two National High School Business Conferences (NHBC) with 300+ cumulative participants
- Co-wrote a case study with Deloitte Canada
- Created content for Instagram account; following increased by 25%

Technical Mentor — Canada (Girls) Learning Code

Toronto, ON | Jan. 2020 - Present

Taught web development to a group of girls using HTML/CSS

President — White Oaks Secondary School (WOSS) DECA Oakville, ON | Sept. 2018 – June 2019

- Led a team of 32 executives, managed 306 members
- Achieved the highest award count in WOSS DECA's 50-year history at Provincials: 116 medals and 29 International qualifiers
- Led social media marketing initiative; club-size increased by 45%

Debate Teaching Assistant — LinkedKey

Mississauga, ON | July 2018 - Aug. 2018

- Taught workshops regarding argument construction and refutation to 22 students
- 2 students became National Champions

SKILLS & QUALIFICATIONS

Programming Java, JavaScript, Python, HTML/CSS, C, Scheme (DrRacket)

Technologies Bootstrap, jQuery, Swing, Visual Studio Code (VS Code), Figma, MS Office

AWARDS

Top Hack out of 128 in Three Categories:

- (1) Best Use of Amazon Web Service (AWS)
- (2) Best Domain
- (3) Most Promising Project

StarterHacks | 2020

3rd Place out of 350 - Harvard College World Schools Debate Tournament

Harvard Speech & Debate Society | 2019

4th Place out of 120 – McMaster University Pro–Am Debate Tournament

McMaster Debating Society | 2019

Graduating Class Salutatorian

White Oaks Secondary School | 2019

Top 8 Oral Competitor – DECA Provincials DECA Ontario | 2018

EDUCATION

University of Waterloo

Candidate for Bachelor of Honours Computer Science, 2024

Sept. 2019 - April 2024 (Projected)

Recipient of the \$2000 President's Scholarship of Distinction for a 97% admission average

Relevant Courses

Designing Functional Programs, Elementary Algorithm Design & Data Abstraction

INTERESTS

Volleyball, running, piano, fashion, photography, photo-editing